I say, "By the way, I think I have
cancer most likely in my mouth and
throat and neck.
I don't know if I should get treatment
or just lay down and die. The only
treatment is radiation and I don't like
that. I'm aware that you don't care
about me and that you hate me and I just
want and you just want to put spells on
me or whatever.
I'm also okay with never seeing or
knowing my daughter. As your family
hates me, you hate me, she's going to
hate me. I just want to say that I've
given up on life and I'm most likely
going to die eventually from the cancer.
It looks like people get what they want.
Get rid of me. So, I'm working on dying.
Just give me some time. It'll happen.
That's what I typed.
>> Then she said,
>> "Why did you message me?" question mark.
I'm not interested in what you have to
say. And I call [__] on the cancer.
Then she said, "Don't message me again.
I'm not interested in hearing anything
from you.
That's abuse."
A few moments later,
The boy who cried wolf, go [__]
yourself. Whoever that person is who
write that, you're a piece of [__] cuz
you're part of the problem. All the
defamation, all the lies. You see, the
amount of the amount the amount of lies,
the amount of lies is what is what has
turned me into the boy who cried wolf.
The thing is that I am always truthful.
I always speak the [__] truth. And
then there's people that speak the
[__] lies. And now the lies have
become the [__] truth. Yeah, that's
what we're dealing with here is that the
lies that people keep telling has become
the truth.
That's my life, right? I have [__]
cancer and I'm [__] going to die. You
can't [__] deal with that. You're
going to tell me I'm a [__] liar for
that. [__] you. [__] you. [__] you.
You're going to make jokes of me for
because of that? [__] you.
Whoever that is, that's so [__]
disrespectful and despicable.
[__] shame on you.
Look at his [__] Look at his [__]
Look at his [__]
Look at this [__] that people are
typing.
Hh.
>> Sorry.
They think it's all a joke.
>> Damn. This is JUST ANOTHER [__] JOKE.
YEAH.
>> HIS CONSTANT lying has led no one to
believe he has cancer. FY.
You've shown us that you will lie to get
out of any situation.